You never know who's listening.
The Night Listener is a crime, horror, mystery
film directed by Patrick Stettner.
In the midst of his crumbling relationship, a radio show host begins
speaking to his biggest fan—a young boy—via the telephone.
But when questions about the boy's identity come up,
the host's life is thrown into chaos.
Gabriel Noone, played by Robin Williams.
Donna D. Logand, played by Toni Collette.
Pete D. Logand, played by Rory Culkin.
Anna, played by Sandra Oh.
Ashe, played by Joe Morton.
Jess, played by Bobby Cannavale.
The Night Listener is a 2006 American psychological thriller film
directed by Patrick Stettner and starring Robin Williams.
The screenplay by Armistead Maupin, Terry Anderson, and Stettner is based on Maupin's
2000 novel The Night Listener, which was inspired by Anthony Godby Johnson.
The film explores themes of new york city, based on novel or
book, aids, radio station, radio presenter.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.